hey everybody welcome to this a one
English listening practice video you can
use this video to practice your
listening and comprehension as I speak
before we start remember to subscribe to
the channel click on the bell and follow
us on Instagram so today I'm gonna talk
about social media nowadays many people
have social media apps on their phones
and computers many people use social
media to communicate with their friends
and family they also use social media
for many other things let's talk about
the different social media apps the most
famous app is Facebook Facebook is very
popular all around the world people all
around the world use Facebook every day
they use Facebook on their computers and
they use Facebook on their phones I
think more people use Facebook on their
phones not their computers Facebook was
invented in 2004 but it wasn't popular
then I started using Facebook in 2010
when did you start using Facebook so
let's talk about what you can do on
Facebook first of all you can use it to
post text pictures and videos when you
post something all your friends can see
it I don't post much on Facebook you can
also use Facebook to send messages you
can send messages to one person or to a
group you can also follow people and
pages on Facebook I follow some news
pages so I can see the news on Facebook
you can do many things on this app but I
don't really like Facebook okay so now
let's talk about Instagram Instagram is
the most popular app for young people
people use this
to post pictures and videos if you like
pictures then you'll probably like
Instagram
I don't like Facebook but I do like
Instagram I like it because it's fun to
look at photos on Instagram you can
follow other people to see their
pictures
some people like following celebrities
and other famous people I don't really
like following celebrities how about you
do you follow any celebrities on
Instagram another thing you can do on
Instagram is post an Instagram story you
can post many photos and videos to your
story
I don't usually post on Instagram but I
look at other people's posts I think
that Instagram is better than Facebook
okay so another social media app that
people use is Twitter I don't have
Twitter so I don't really know how to
use it but I know that it's a very
popular app all around the world many
people use this app to follow the news
people post news stories on Twitter I
don't need a Twitter account because I
can read the news on Facebook another
app that young people use is snapchat I
had snapchat when I was younger but now
I don't
people use snapchat to send pictures and
short videos to each other then these
pictures and videos disappear after you
view them there are many other social
media apps too the world loves social
media alright that's all for today leave
a comment and tell me which social media
app you like best and remember to
subscribe to the channel click on the
Bell and follow us on Instagram for more
English tips and lessons I'll see you
next time
[Music]
[Applause]